What's this, Link?
It's from the old SAO server.
I wonder who it could be.
let's do it once again.
I don't know what the truth is.
I don't know what it is, but...
I don't know
what the
truth is.
Ah! Ah!
Hello, anyone in there?
Looking for the black swordsman?
Come on, sunshine.
Get your ass up already.
During the battle, he kept trying to move
to get up, and then he started crying.
Easy, Ronie.
What is wrong with you?
Can't you see he's hurt?
He's not in any shape to defend himself!
We surrendered just like you
wanted, so leave him alone already!
Are you gonna keep sitting
there and doing nothing?
That ain't no fun at all, tough guy!
Yo, rise and shine, asswife! Stand up!
Good morning!
Head!
Damn, that's tragic.
Looks like he really is busted.
The great hero's just a vegetable now.
So, you can move.
What's up you want me
to give this back to you
come
on man
say something son
of a bitch get your hands off him god
damn it I'm gonna
kill you you bastard
Whoever you are, you're dead.
Oh my god.
Eiji?
You little turd, get out of my face!
We got another hacker here.
Send his cheating ass back to Japan.
Yuna, I came as fast as I could.
It's Yuna. No way.
It is her.
You ready, Eiji?
Oh, yeah, she gonna
stand there do something
Round two coming up.
I know that voice!
It's Yuna!
Wait, then this really
is a Japanese server?
Bastard.
Who are you?
Your past.
I'm a knight of the blood oath.
I'm Nautilus!
I never heard of you, you jackass!
Yeah, I guess you wouldn't have.
Back then, I was useless and weak.
Not anymore!
In Aincrad, you were a murderer.
Some of the people you
killed were my friends!
This is payback!
This is for them!
I don't know.
Oh
Look at this Japanese gamer trash
You pissant
You never had a chance in hell against me
I should have had you aborted
Ever since you slithered
out You've been nothing
but a curse on my life.
You're a demon.
I'm glad to see you're looking healthy.
Yeah, like you ever cared.
I haven't seen you in years, Dad.
What do you want?
My son, your older half-brother,
suffers from congenital kidney failure.
He needs a kidney transplant
as soon as possible.
And why are you telling me this?
I found the best hospital
in Japan for the procedure,
along with a top surgeon to perform it.
So?
I want you to donate one
of your kidneys to my son.
What the hell?
Get someone else!
If you refuse, I can't support
you or your mother anymore.
Goddamn Japanese!
We're coming to you live in front
of Tokorozawa General Hospital,
where victims of the SAO incident have
been arriving by ambulance non-stop.
Since the game went live three days ago,
officials have yet to find a solution.
Meanwhile, the death toll reached 478,
and that number is expected to climb.
The police are currently at work
rounding up all NerveGear consoles.
On the black market,
however, they are still here.
Going shopping.
Link, start.
You're a demon.
Nothin' I hate more than the Japanese,
and now I can kill all I want.
Nice try, Nichi.
You Japanese all fight the same.
All sizzle, no steak.
Time to say sayonara.
In the end, I still
took a piece out of you.
You lousy, rotten, asswipe!
Yuna, I did my job as a
knight this time, didn't I?
Yes, Eiji, you did.
His hand, you see the logo on it?
Yeah, it's the same as the one the members
of Laughing Coffin head, Laughing Coffin?
Yeah, they went around
killing people in SAO.
He's one of them, a serial killer.
What is that?
It's mind control! Calm down! Stop!
You have to fight it!
That guy's a serial killer!
Snap out of it!
He's controlling you!
He wants us to kill each other!
Dude, you're not thinking straight!
Everyone!
Stand down and listen to us!
Is he a demon? What?
Don't worry, pal.
You'll be back on your feet real soon.
And I promise to keep the killing
going until you decide to.
The Hecate II holds seven rounds
per mag, and I got one round left.
A Barrett XM-500 rifle
holds ten rounds per mag.
That means he's got two left.
Verderous anima!
It's like a curse.
The Terraria account has
unlimited regeneration.
So no matter how bad I'm hurt.
Or how much pain I feel.
I can't die out.
If Kazuto were in my place.
He wouldn't care.
He'd keep going.
So I'll keep going too.
I can do this.
I'll cut all of them down myself.
After all I'm Kazuto's and
Kirito the Black Swords Mints.
Little sister!
Ah-ah-ah!
I won't give up.
My imagination transformed
Solas' bow into my rifle.
But I bet I can still access the
original system features of the bow.
No way am I giving up.
I have to believe in me,
in Hecate, in Kirito.
By automatically absorbing
the resources around it,
the bow can recharge its main
attack, the Annihilation Ray.
Save us!
Oh yeah, and I got plenty
more where that came from!
Kiwi-to.
I...
I put up a good fight.
I'll cause a toll.
Higa, look out!
Higa!
You okay?
Answer me!
Yeah, I'm okay. Just freaked out.
I didn't know you could scream so loud.
How in the hell can you be so calm?
Are you hurt?
Did he shoot you?
Oh, well, um...
No, not really.
He just winged me.
But I'm okay to keep going here.
So don't worry about me.
Just make sure Kirito's stable.
Are you sure you're okay?
You better not be lying to me.
If you are, I'm gonna kick your butt.
I'm not lying, I swear. I'm fine.
All right, I'm going back to Subcon then.
I'll let you know if Kirito's
condition changes any.
Good luck, Higa!
Rank, wait! What?
I was sort of wondering...
Do you want to get some food sometime?
When this is all over?
Yeah, of course.
Hamburgers, beef bowls, whatever
you want to eat, you got it.
My treat.
That'll be a cheap date.
I probably jinxed it by asking her anyway.
Connecting STL one to four.
Connecting five and six.
All right. Kitty Tom.
Let's wake you up already.
Please, Kirito.
I'll give my heart, my life, everything.
Please, please, open your eyes.
Kazuto.
Kirito!
Come on, Kirito.
Kirito?
Was it all a dream?
Thank you so much for watching.
Thank you.